<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> <rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://austintexas.gov/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <channel> <title>AustinGO RSS</title>
 <description>News from Austintexas.gov - The Official Website of the City of Austin</description>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/</link>
 <atom:link rel="self" href="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml" />
 <item> <title>June 2015 busiest month ever at AUS</title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/june-2015-busiest-month-ever-aus</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;AUSTIN, TEXAS – June 2015 set another airport monthly passenger record with 1,088,399 traveling through Austin-Bergstrom International Airport. This is the sixth monthly record to be broken in the past 16 months and the fourth 1 million passenger month in airport history— third of this year. The previous airport monthly record of 1,022,353 was set in May 2015. Austin’s airport has experienced passenger growth in 33 consecutive months, 65 of the last 66 dating back to January 2010.&lt;/p&gt;...</description>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36201 </guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 10:38:06 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
 <item> <title>City launches action plan to improve development-related services for Austin customers </title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/city-launches-action-plan-improve-development-related-services-austin-customers</link>
 <description>&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The City of Austin Development Services Department and Planning and Zoning Department launched a “Roadmap to Success” today for improving the customer experience with development review, permitting, inspection services, and planning.&lt;br /&gt;
		 &lt;br /&gt;
		The Roadmap, which includes input from all levels of department employees, represents a customer-centric approach to implement recommendations provided by Zucker Systems, a management and process consulting firm...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36172 </guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 00:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
 <item> <title>City of Austin to Implement Initiatives and Develop Long-Term Plan in Response to Austin Music Census</title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/city-austin-implement-initiatives-and-develop-long-term-plan-response-austin-music-census</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;The City of Austin Music &amp;amp; Entertainment Division of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://austintexas.us5.list-manage.com/track/click?u=1861810ce1dca1a4c1673747c&amp;amp;id=6458e8eb23&amp;amp;e=19f502a936&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Economic Development Department&lt;/a&gt; has spent the past eight weeks reviewing the data of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://austintexas.us5.list-manage.com/track/click?u=1861810ce1dca1a4c1673747c&amp;amp;id=b661c6337d&amp;amp;e=19f502a936&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Austin Music Census&lt;/a&gt;, and is working to develop a...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36184 </guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 17:50:20 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
 <item> <title>Cast Your Vote for Barton Springs Lifeguards</title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/cast-your-vote-barton-springs-lifeguards</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Lifeguards working at Barton Springs Pool for the City of Austin, Parks and Recreation Department&#039;s Aquatic Division were selected to compete in Good Morning America’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://austintexas.us5.list-manage.com/track/click?u=1861810ce1dca1a4c1673747c&amp;amp;id=e11796d66e&amp;amp;e=de3f80ba0f&quot;&gt;Lifeguard Surf &amp;amp; Turf Showdown&lt;/a&gt;. One of five semi-finalists, the Barton Springs Lifeguards answered the ABC morning show’s call for lifeguards around the country to lip-sync to the song “Shut Up...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36178 </guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 15:03:13 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
 <item> <title>City seeks applications from nonprofits for Holly Good Neighbor Program ($1.2M available)</title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/city-seeks-applications-nonprofits-holly-good-neighbor-program-12m-available</link>
 <description>&lt;h4&gt;
	&lt;u&gt;SUMMARY&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Austin Housing Finance Corporation (AHFC) announces the upcoming availability of&lt;strong&gt; $1.2 million&lt;/strong&gt; in funding for the Holly Good Neighbor (HGN) Program and currently seeks applications from experienced nonprofit organizations to provide home repair and rehabilitation services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Services will benefit low- to moderate-income families and individuals whose household income is at or below 100 percent of the Area Median Family Income (AMFI) as...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36171 </guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 14:27:54 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
 <item> <title>Fatality Crash #57</title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/fatality-crash-57-0</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Case:  &lt;/strong&gt;           2015-1961576&lt;br /&gt;
	          &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date:   &lt;/strong&gt;           Wednesday, July 15, 2015&lt;br /&gt;
	             &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:    &lt;/strong&gt;          8:07 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;	&lt;strong&gt;Location:  &lt;/strong&gt;     9100 block of RM 2222&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;	&lt;strong&gt;Deceased:  &lt;/strong&gt;   Cale Ferguson, White male (D.O.B. 7-6-1960)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;	The preliminary investigation shows that the driver of a white 2015 Chevrolet Tahoe was traveling northbound in the 9100 block of RM 2222...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36170 </guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 13:21:13 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
 <item> <title>Don&amp;#039;t Block the Box Shifting Locations</title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/dont-block-box-shifting-locations-0</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Beginning Monday, July, 27, 2015, APD Officers and the City of Austin Transportation Department will be shifting locations enforcing the Don’t Block the Box campaign. Officers will be at the following key intersections to keep traffic flowing during the peak travel times of 7-9 a.m. and 4-6:30 p.m.:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	• William Cannon at Bluff Springs&lt;br /&gt;
	• Parmer Lane at Lamar Blvd.&lt;br /&gt;
	• Rundberg Lane at Middle Fiskville&lt;br /&gt;
	• William Cannon at Brodie Lane&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Officers at the...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36169 </guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 11:59:36 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
 <item> <title>City Announces Partnership with GivePulse</title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/city-announces-partnership-givepulse-0</link>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36167 </guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 11:21:32 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
 <item> <title>City of Austin Asks Residents How to Increase Recycling</title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/city-austin-asks-residents-how-increase-recycling</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Austin Resource Recovery is asking residents to help them increase Austin’s recycling. July 27 through August 24, Austinites can share their insights about recycling through an online survey, text messages and community meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A recent study found that 44 percent of things thrown in the trash could be recycled. This means that more recyclables go in the trash than the recycling cart. The City wants to learn from residents what is causing this problem and what might solve it.&lt;/p&gt;...</description>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36164 </guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 09:51:26 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
 <item> <title>Planned Unit Development Density Bonus: Stakeholder Workshop on Implementation Recommendations</title>
 <link>http://austintexas.gov/news/planned-unit-development-density-bonus-stakeholder-workshop-implementation-recommendations</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Join Neighborhood Housing and Community Development (NHCD) on Thursday, July 30, 2015 at 11:30 am for a collaborative work session related to draft proposed amendments to the City of Austin Land Development Code related to the Planned Unit Development Density Bonus Program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This work session is an opportunity for stakeholders to collaborate with each other and NHCD staff to develop a draft framework for how the fee-in-lieu request process could be implemented if the City Council were...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">atx36163 </guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 09:04:28 CDT</pubDate>
 <source url="http://austintexas.gov/site/news/rss.xml">AustinGO RSS</source>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
